A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Natural Resources, 1992-2006 (bulk 2002-2005)
Library of Virginia
- Series IV. Correspondence and Supporting Documents, Constituent, 2002-2006., Extent: 10.7 cu. ft. (Box 59-89.)
  - Series V. Correspondence and Supporting Documents, Secretary W. Tayloe Murphy, Jr., 1997-2006., Extent: 6.1 cu. ft. (Box 90-107.)
    - Governor-Related Files--Warner 2001 Natural Resources Briefing Papers, 2001. (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Governor-Related Files--Warner 2001 Natural Resources Briefing Papers, 2001. (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Governor-Related Files--Warner 2001 Natural Resources Briefing Papers, 2001. (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Governor-Related Files--Wilder Commission, 2002. (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - James River Association, 2000-2002. (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - James River Association, 2002. (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - James River Association, 2002-2005. (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Nature Conservancy, 2002-2003. (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Nature Conservancy, 2003-2004. (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Nature Conservancy, 2005. (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Reading File, 2002 December. (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Reading File, 2002 December. (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Reading File, 2002 November. (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Reading File, 2002 November. (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Reading File, 2002 October. (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Reading File, 2002 October. (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Reading File, 2002 October. (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Reading File, 2002 September. (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Reading File, 2002 September. (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Reading File, 2002 August. (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Reading File, 2002 August. (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Reading File, 2002 July. (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Reading File, 2002 July. (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Reading File, 2002 July. (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Reading File, 2002 June. (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Reading File, 2002 June. (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Reading File, 2002 May. (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Reading File, 2002 May. (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Reading File, 2002 May. (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Reading File, 2002 April. (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - Reading File, 2002 April. (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - Reading File, 2002 April. (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Reading File, 2002 April. (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Reading File, 2002 March. (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Reading File, 2002 February. (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Reading File, 2002 February. (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Reading File, 2002 February. (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Reading File, 2002 January. (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Reading File, 2003 December. (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Reading File, 2003 December. (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Reading File, 2003 December. (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Reading File, 2003 November. (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Reading File, 2003 November. (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Reading File, 2003 October. (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Reading File, 2003 October. (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Reading File, 2003 October. (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - Reading File, 2003 September. (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - Reading File, 2003 September. (Box 98, Folder 17)
    - Reading File, 2003 September. (Box 98, Folder 18)
    - Reading File, 2003 September. (Box 98, Folder 19)
    - Reading File, 2003 August. (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Reading File, 2003 July. (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Reading File, 2003 July. (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Reading File, 2003 July. (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Reading File, 2003 July. (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Reading File, 2003 June. (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Reading File, 2003 June. (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Reading File, 2003 June. (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Reading File, 2003 May. (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Reading File, 2003 May. (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Reading File, 2003 May. (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Reading File, 2003 April. (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Reading File, 2003 April. (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Reading File, 2003 April. (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Reading File, 2003 March. (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Reading File, 2003 March. (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - Reading File, 2003 March. (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - Reading File, 2003 February. (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - Reading File, 2003 February. (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Reading File, 2003 February. (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Reading File, 2003 January. (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Reading File, 2004 December. (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Reading File, 2004 December. (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Reading File, 2004 December. (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Reading File, 2004 November. (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Reading File, 2004 November. (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Reading File, 2004 November. (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Reading File, 2004 November. (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Reading File, 2004 October. (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Reading File, 2004 October. (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Reading File, 2004 October. (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Reading File, 2004 October. (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Reading File, 2004 September. (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Reading File, 2004 August. (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Reading File, 2004 August. (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Reading File, 2004 August. (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Reading File, 2004 July. (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Reading File, 2004 July. (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Reading File, 2004 July. (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Reading File, 2004 June. (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Reading File, 2004 May. (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Reading File, 2004 May. (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Reading File, 2004 April. (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Reading File, 2004 April. (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Reading File, 2004 April. (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Reading File, 2004 March. (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Reading File, 2004 March. (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - Reading File, 2004 March. (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - Reading File, 2004 February. (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - Reading File, 2004 February. (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Reading File, 2004 February. (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Reading File, 2004 February. (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Reading File, 2004 February. (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Reading File, 2004 February. (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Reading File, 2004 January. (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Reading File, 2004 January. (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Reading File, 2004 January. (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Reading File, 2004 January. (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Reading File, 2004 January. (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Reading File, 2005 December. (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Reading File, 2005 December. (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Reading File, 2005 November. (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Reading File, 2005 October. (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - Reading File, 2005 October. (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - Reading File, 2005 September. (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - Reading File, 2005 August. (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Reading File, 2005 August. (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Reading File, 2005 August. (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Reading File, 2005 July. (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Reading File, 2005 July. (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Reading File, 2005 July. (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Reading File, 2005 June. (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Reading File, 2005 June. (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Reading File (FOIA Request), 2005 June. (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Reading File (FOIA Request), 2005 June. (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Reading File (FOIA Request), 2005 June. (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Reading File, 2005 May. (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Reading File, 2005 April. (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Reading File, 2005 April. (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Reading File, 2005 March. (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Reading File, 2005 March. (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Reading File, 2005 March. (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Reading File, 2005 February. (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Reading File, 2005 February. (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Reading File, 2005 January. (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Reading File, 2005 January. (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Reading File, 2006 January. (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Resumes and Recommendations, 2001-2002. (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Resumes and Recommendations, 2002. (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Resumes and Recommendations, 2002. (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Resumes and Recommendations, 2003. (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Resumes and Recommendations, 2004. (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Resumes and Recommendations, 2005. (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Resumes and Recommendations, 2005. (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Transportation, Department of, 1997-1998. (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Department of, 2001-2002. (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Transportation, Department of, 2002-2003. (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Transportation, Department of, 2003-2004. (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Transportation, Department of, 2005. (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - United States Commission on Ocean Policy, 2004. (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - United States Commissio on Ocean Policy, 2004. (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Urban Sprawl / Smart Growth, 2000. (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Urban Sprawl / Smart Growth, 2001-2002. (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Urban Sprawl / Smart Growth, 2002. (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Urban Sprawl / Smart Growth, 2003. (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University--Rice Environmental Center, 2002-2003. (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University--Rice Environmental Center, 2002-2003. (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Information Providers Network (VIPNET), 1999-2002. (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Institute of Marine Science (VIMS), 1998-2002. (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Institute of Marine Science (VIMS), 1998-2002. (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Tourism Corporation, 2000-2002. (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Tourism Corporation, 2002. (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Tourism Corporation, 2002. (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Tourism Corporation, 2002. (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Tourism Corporation, 2002. (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Tourism Corporation, 2002. (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Tourism Corporation, 2002-2005. (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund Guidelines (Revisions), 2005. (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund Guidelines (Revisions), 2005. (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund Guidelines (Revisions), 2005. (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund Guidelines (Revisions), 2005. (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund Guidelines (Revisions), 2005. (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund Guidelines (Revisions), 2005. (Box 107, Folder 3)
- Series VI. Decision Briefs, 2001-2006., Extent: 1 folder. (Box 107.)
  Contains decision briefs and related documents pertaining to the disbursement of monies from the Virginia Environmental Emergency Response Fund. Approval from the Governor is required for disbursements of more than $100,000. Emergencies include the Starlight Lane tire fire in Roanoke (2002), and a Superfund site in Suffolk (2005).
  Arranged chronologically. (Accessions 42294 and 42398).
  - Virginia Environmental Emergency Response Fund, 2001-2006. (Box 107, Folder 4)
- Series VII. Legislative Initiatives, 2002-2005., Extent: 4.2 cu. ft. (Box 108-119.)
  Contains legislative records created and maintained by the Office of the Secretary of Natural Resources. The files include enrolled bill reviews, legislative action summaries, proposals and other items that document the legislative process. The bills and files here are related only to natural resources issues and agendas. Included in the material are opinions from the Secretary, as well as the agencies directly affected by the proposed legislation. The "graveyard" files include bills that were tabled or voted down. A few subject files are included here such as those that document the proposed tipping fee associated with interstate waste dumping (2002), the merger of the Chesapeake Local Assistance Department into the Department of Conservation and Recreation (2003), and issues surrounding the Water Quality Improvement Fund (2005). Some of the files many contain documents from the preceeding year, but were considered part of the General Assembly session for the following calendar year. The "Legislative Session" folders usually contain general information on the legislative activities of the Secretariat, unless a subtitle is noted.
  Arranged chronologically by General Assembly session, then alphabetically within. Most of the bill files are arranged chronologically, though some may not be. Original order and titles of the files were maintained. (Accessions 42294 and 42398).
  - 2002 General Assembly.
    - 2002 Legislative Session (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - 2002 Legislative Session (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - 2002 Legislative Session (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - 2002 Legislative Session (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Bond Referendum (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - HJR 159 Survey (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - HJR 159 Survey (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - HJR 159 Survey (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - HJR 159 Survey (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - HJR 159 Survey (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - HJR 159 Survey (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - HJR 159 Survey (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Tipping Fee Notebook (SB 592) (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - Tipping Fee Notebook (SB 592) (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - Tipping Fee Notebook (SB 592) (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - Tipping Fee Notebook (SB 592) (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Tipping Fee Notebook (SB 592) (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Tipping Fee Notebook (SB 592) (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Tipping Fee Notebook (SB 592) (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Tipping Fee Notebook (SB 592) (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Tipping Fee Notebook (SB 592) (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - 2003 General Assembly.
    - 2003 Legislative Session (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - 2003 Legislative Session (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - 2003 Legislative Session (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - 2003 Legislative Session (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - 2003 Legislative Session (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - 2003 Legislative Session (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - 2003 Legislative Session--Adequate Public Facilities Ordinances (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - 2003 Legislative Session--Adequate Public Facilities Ordinances (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - 2003 Legislative Session--SB 1116 (CBLAD Merger) (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - 2003 Legislative Session--SB 1116 (CBLAD Merger) (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - 2003 Legislative Session--SB 1116 (CBLAD Merger) (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - 2003 Legislative Session--Slaughter, Kay (Water Control Board) (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - 2003 Legislative Session--Slaughter, Kay (Water Control Board) (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - 2003 Legislative Session--Slaughter, Kay (Water Control Board) (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - 2003 Legislative Session--HB 1481 (Waterfowl Sanctuaries and Blinds) (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - 2003 Legislative Session--Enrolled Bill Reviews (House and Senate) (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - 2003 Legislative Session--Enrolled Bill Reviews (House and Senate) (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - 2003 Legislative Session--Enrolled Bill Reviews (House and Senate) (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - 2003 Legislative Session--Enrolled Bill Reviews (House and Senate) (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - 2003 Legislative Session--Enrolled Bill Reviews (House and Senate) (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - 2003 Legislative Session--Enrolled Bill Reviews (House and Senate) (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Graveyard (House and Senate Bills) (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Graveyard (House and Senate Bills) (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Graveyard (House and Senate Bills) (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Graveyard (House and Senate Bills) (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Graveyard (House and Senate Bills) (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Graveyard (House and Senate Bills) (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Graveyard (House and Senate Bills) (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Graveyard (House and Senate Bills) (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Graveyard (House and Senate Bills) (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Graveyard (House and Senate Bills) (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Graveyard (House and Senate Bills) (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Graveyard (House and Senate Bills) (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Graveyard (House and Senate Bills) (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Graveyard (House and Senate Bills) (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Graveyard (House and Senate Bills) (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--House Bills (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--House Bills (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--House Bills (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--House Bills (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--House Bills (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--House Bills (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Legislative Proposals (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Legislative Proposals (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Legislative Proposals (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Legislative Proposals (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Legislative Proposals (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Legislative Proposals (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Legislative Proposals (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Legislative Proposals (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Legislative Proposals (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Senate Bills (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Senate Bills (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Senate Bills (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Senate Bills (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Senate Bills (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Senate Bills (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Senate Bills (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Senate Bills (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Natural Resources 2003 Legislation--Senate Bills (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - 2004 General Assembly.
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--Enrolled Bill Reviews (House) (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--Enrolled Bill Reviews (House) (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--Enrolled Bill Reviews (House) (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--Enrolled Bill Reviews (House) (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--Enrolled Bill Reviews (House) (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--Enrolled Bill Reviews (House) (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--Enrolled Bill Reviews (House) (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--Enrolled Bill Reviews (Senate) (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--Enrolled Bill Reviews (Senate) (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--Enrolled Bill Reviews (Senate) (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--Graveyard (House) (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--Graveyard (House) (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--Graveyard (House) (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--Graveyard (House) (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--Graveyard (Senate) (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--Graveyard (Senate) (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--Graveyard (Senate) (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--House Bills (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--House Bills (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--House Bills (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--House Bills (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--House Bills (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--House Bills (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--House Bills (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--House Bills (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--House Bills (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--Senate Bills (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--Senate Bills (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--Senate Bills (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - Natural Resources 2004 Legislation--Senate Bills (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - Nutrient Allocations (SB 639) (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Subaqueous Lands (SB 606) (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Subaqueous Lands (SB 606) (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Marine Resources Commission Fees (HB 1024) (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - 2005 General Assembly.
    - Duck Blinds (DGIF) (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Enrolled Bill Reviews (House) (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Enrolled Bill Reviews (House) (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Enrolled Bill Reviews (House) (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Enrolled Bill Reviews (House) (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Enrolled Bill Reviews (House) (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - Enrolled Bill Reviews (House) (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - Enrolled Bill Reviews (House) (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - Enrolled Bill Reviews (House) (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - Enrolled Bill Reviews (Senate) (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - Enrolled Bill Reviews (Senate) (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Enrolled Bill Reviews (Senate) (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Enrolled Bill Reviews (Senate) (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Graveyard (House) (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Graveyard (House) (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Graveyard (House) (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Graveyard (Senate) (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Graveyard (Senate) (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Legislative Action Summaries (House) (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Legislative Action Summaries (House) (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Legislative Action Summaries (House) (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Legislative Action Summaries (House) (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Legislative Action Summaries (House) (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Legislative Action Summaries (House) (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Legislative Action Summaries (House) (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - Legislative Action Summaries (House) (Box 117, Folder 16)
    - Legislative Action Summaries (Senate) (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Legislative Action Summaries (Senate) (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Legislative Action Summaries (Senate) (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Legislative Action Summaries (Senate) (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Legislative Package (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Legislative Package (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Nutrient Credit Trading (HB 2862) (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Nutrient Credit Trading (HB 2862) (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Nutrient Credit Trading (HB 2862) (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Offshore Natural Gas Study (HJR 625) (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Offshore Natural Gas Study (HJR 625) (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Offshore Natural Gas Study (HJR 625) (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Offshore Natural Gas Study (HJR 625) (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund Legislation (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund Legislation (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund Legislation (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund Legislation (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Water Quality Improvement Fund Legislation (Box 119, Folder 3)